PHATUTSHEDZO MAKUSHU

<u>0792883338</u> <u>phatumakushu@gmail.com</u> <u>LinkedIn</u> <u>Portfolio</u> <u>Github</u>

About Me

I love creating responsive web content using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery and PHP. With my skills and experience, I am a force to be reckoned with in order to make the world a better place.

Skills

Angular | ASP.Net | C# | CSS | HTML | JavaScript | jQuery | PHP | Silverlight | WPF

Experience

Jun 2019 - Present

GirlCode | Web Developer Facilitator

Responsible for teaching high scholars to code from scratch with Scratch.

FEB 2020 - Present

BBD Software Development | Web Developer Intern

Responsible for ASP.Net applications, MSSQL to POSTGRES migration and Angular applications.

Education

MAR 2019 - FEB 2020

<u>Umuzi Academy</u> National certificate in Information Technology

JUL 2017 – DEC 2018

<u>Tshwane University of Technology</u> BTech in Information Technology

JAN 2014 - JUN 2017

<u>Tshwane University of Technology</u> National Diploma in Information Technology

JAN 2013 – DEC 2013

Rand Hills College | National Senior Certificate